Guide to the Office of Public Affairs, Yale University, Photographs of Individuals
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Photographs of Yale Faculty, Circa 1966-2005; Accession 2011-A-025
  - Guicharnaud, Jacques, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Guido, Louis J., 1993 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Gunnoud, Patricia T., 1985 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Guyet, Allan R., 1990, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Gyorgyey, Clara, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Haas, Lawrence J., 1986 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Habeck, Mary R., 1999 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Hack, John, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Hackman, Judith, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Hager, Gregory, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Hahm, Shinik, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Hall, John Whitney, Undated (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Hallo, William W., 1983, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Halsey, Ralph Jr., 1980 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Hamada, Koichi, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Hamburger, Joseph, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Hamlin, Cyrus, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Hammer, Langdon, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Hammond, Dr. Graeme, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Handschumacher, Robert E, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Hanks, Toby, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Hansen, Valerie, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Hansmann, Henry B., 1997 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Hanson, Anne C., 1978, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Hanson, F. Fay, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Harada, Sadao, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Harries, Karsten, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Harris, Walter DeS, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Harshav, Benjamin, 1987, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Harath, Sidney, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Hartigan, John A., 1990 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Hartman, Geoffrey, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Hartman, Willard D., 1991, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Hauer, Erwin F., 1990 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Hauser, Susan, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Hausser, Penny, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Hawkshaw, Paul, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Hayden, Bernard J., 1977 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Hayden, Dolores, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Hayes, Christine, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Hayes, Mark M.D., Undated (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Hazard, Geoffrey, Undated (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Head, Thomas F., 1991 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Heath, Fenno, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Heath, Fenno, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Hein, Norvin J., 1978 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Hendon, Rufus S., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Henrich, Janet B., 1984 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Herington, John, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Hersey, George, 1990, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Hexter, Jack H., 1975 (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - Hickey, Leo J., 1990 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Hicks, R. Lansing, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Hierholzer, Walter, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Highbaugh, Claudia, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Hill, Andrew, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Hill, Charles, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Hilton, Allen, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Hockfield, Susan, 1998, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Hoffleit, Dorrit, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Hoffman, Gail, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Hoffman, Joseph, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Hohenberg, Pierre, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Holcombe, Terry, 1978, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Holden IV, Reuben A., 1971, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Holder, Angela R., 1985 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Hole, Frank, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Hollander, John, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Hollingsworth, Andrew, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Holloway, Frances, 1985, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Holloway, Jonathan, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Holmer, Paul L., 1987 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Holmes, Frederic L., 1979 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Holquist, Michael, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Homans, Margaret, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Horn, Laurence, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Horowitz, Nina M.D., Undated (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Horstmann, Dorothy M., 1980 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Horvath, Csaba, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Horwitz, Ralph Dr., 1991 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Howard, Sir Michael, 1989, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Howe, Christine, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Howe, Roger E., 1987, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Hramov, Emilia, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Hsiung, G.D. M.D., 1989 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Hsu, Mary Li, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Huber, Gregory, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Hudak, Paul, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Huebner, Dwayne, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Huffer, Lynne, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Hughes, Vernon, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Hunt, Eileen, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - hunt, Marilyn, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Hunter, George K., 1985, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Huszar, Gabor B., 1984 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Hutchinson, Franklin, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Huynh, Sanh-Thong, 1987, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Hyman, Paula, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Iachello, Francesco, 1990, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Ibbotson, Roger G., Undated (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Ickovics, Jeannette, 1997, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Ihinger, Phillip D., Undated (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Iino, Catherine, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Ingersoll, Jonathan, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Insler, Stanley, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Isomura, Kazuhide, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Izenour, George C., Undated (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Jackson, Robert L., 1991, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Jackson, Robert P., Undated (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Jackson, K. David, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Jackson, Stanley, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Jacob, Rich, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Jacobson, Nathan, Undated (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Jacoby, Dr. Robert O., 1987 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Jamieson, James M.D., 1989 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Janeway, Charles A., Undated (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Jason, Lois K., 1988 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Jatlow, Peter M.D., 1983 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Jaynes, Gerald, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Jekel, James F., 1982 (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Johns, Michael E., 1989 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Johnson, Marcia, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - Johnson, Mark, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Johnson, Nancy K., 1988 (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Johnson, Robert C., 1990 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Jokl, Peter M.D., 1976 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Jones, Philip, Undated (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Jones, Rosemary, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Jones, Stephen B., Undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Jorgensen, William, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Joseph, Gilbert M., Undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Jovin, Suzanne, Undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Kagan. Donald, 1976, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Kagan, Shelly, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Kahn, Paul W., 1996 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Kakutani, Shizuo, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Kane, Patricia E., 1985 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Kannan, Ravindran, Undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Kantor, Fred M.D., 1982 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Kao, Charles K., 1986 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Kapadia, Shanta (MBB), 1984 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Kaplan, Carla, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Kaplan, Louis J., 1990 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Karchin, Paul E., 1988 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Kashgarian, Michael, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Katz, Ruth, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Kauder, Helen, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Kavanagh, Aidan Reve., 1984 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Kazdin, Prof. Alan E., 1992, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Kazemzadeth, Firuz, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Keck, Leander Rev., 1979, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Keck, Margaret, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Keggi, Kristaps M.D., Undated (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Keil, Frank, 1998, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Keller, Michael, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Kellert, Stephen, 1990, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Kelley, Brooks M., Undated (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Kellogg, Augustus, Undated (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Kelly, Cynthia D., 1989, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Kelly, William S., 1992 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Kelly, William W., 2000 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Kelsey, David H. (Rev.), 1993 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Kennedy, Paul M., 1988 - 1992 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Kerbel, Michael, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Kerr, Chester, 1978, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Keshishian, Haig, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Kessen, William, 1978 - 1988 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Kessler, David, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Kevles, Daniel, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Keyes, David E., 1991 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Kezerian, Stephen, Undated (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Kiang, Lindsey, Undated (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Kidd, Kenneth, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Kiernan, Ben, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Kim, Jung H., 1982 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Kimball, Anne, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Kimball, Eugene, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Kinder, Barbara (M.D.), Undated (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Kindlmann, Peter J., Undated (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - King, Laura, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Kiphuth, Delaney, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Kirchner, J. Cameron, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Kirchner, John A. (M.D.), 1984 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Kirkpatrick, John, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Klasky, Helaine, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Kleiner, Diane E.E., 1998 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Klin, Ami J., 1999 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Koetter, Fred H., 1992 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Koh, Harold Hongju, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Kohorn, Ernest (M.D.), 1977 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Kolligan, John, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Komp, Diane (M.D.), 1992 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Konigsberg, William, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Kordak, Mary, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Korner, Stephan, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Kosten, Dr. Thomas, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - Kozak, Sgt. Russell, 1989, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - Krauss, Judith, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - Kraybill, Henry, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Kriegman, David J., 1990 (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - Krigbaum, Charles, 1981, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - Kronman, Anthony, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - Krystal, John H., 1995 (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - Kubler, George A., 1991 (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - Kuc, Roman, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - Kuchen, Dick, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 78)
  - Kunz, Diane B., 1990, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 79)
  - LaDa-Mocarski, Polly, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Laderman, Ezra, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - LaFrance, Marianne, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Laimon, Sara, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Lalli, Richard, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Lamar, Howard R, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - LaMotte, Robert H., Undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Landau, Paul, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Lane, Cecil T., Undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Lane, Robert E., 1976 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Lang, Serge Prof., 1982 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Langbein, John H., 1999 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Lanman, William K., 2001 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Lapinski, John S., 1999 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - LaPolombara, Joseph, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Lara, Rev. Jaime, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Larson, Bruce, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Larson, John B., 1995 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Larson, Richard B., 1979, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Lasaga, Antonio, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Lasker, Daniel, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Lassonde, Stephen, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Laub, Dori, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Laurans, Penelope, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Lawson, Jack P., Undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Lawler, Traugott, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Layton, Bentley, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Leadbeater, Bonnie, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Lear, Jonathan, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Leavy, Stanley (M.D.), Undated (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Leckman, Dr. James, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Lee, Dr. Forrester A., 1997 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Lee, Xuhai, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Lees, Jonathan, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Lengyel, Peter, Undated (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Leonard, Martha (M.D.), 1986 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Lerner, Aaron (M.D.), 1991 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Lerner, Michael (M.D.), 1984 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Leslie, Kristen, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Letriz-Nunez, Edgar, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Levin, Jane, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Levine, Jesse, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Levine, Robert J. (M.D.), Undated (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Levinson, Daniel J., 1990-2002 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Levitin, Howard (M.D.), Undated (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Lewis, Melvin (M.D.), Undated (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Lewis, Richard W.B., 1982, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Lhamon, Judith A., 1986 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Liberman, Alvin M., 1978 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Liberman, Rosette, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Lichten, William L., 1986 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Lidz, Theodore, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Liebert, Herman W., Undated (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Lifset, Reif, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Lifton, Norman, Undated (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Lifton, Richard, Undated (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Lindbeck, George A., 1980 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Lindblom, Charles, 1979, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Lindblom, Edward, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Lindskog, Gustav (M.D.), Undated (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Linz, Juan J., 1989 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Lipson, Rita (Brackman), 1992 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Logan, Anne-Marie, Undated (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Long, Charles, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Long, Marshall, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Lopez, Claude Anne, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Lopez-de-Silanes, Florencio, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - Lord, George DeForest, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Lorimer, Linda Koch, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - Lorimer, Linda Koch, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - Lorimer, Linda Koch, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - Lorkovic, Tatjana, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - Lott, John, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - Lounsbury, Floyd, Undated (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - Lovasz, Laszlo, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - Lu, Daniel C.J., Undated (Box 10, Folder 76)
  - Lu, Vivien, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - Lubell, Michael, Undated (Box 10, Folder 78)
  - Lubin, Hadar, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 79)
  - Luftig, Victor, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 80)
  - Lustman, Jeffrey, Undated (Box 10, Folder 81)
  - Lustman-Findley, Katherine, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 82)
  - Lyons, Philip A., 1985 (Box 10, Folder 83)
  - Lytle, W. Richard, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 84)
  - Lytton, Bernard (M.D.), 1992 (Box 10, Folder 85)
  - Ma, Tso-Ping, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 86)
  - MacAvoy, Paul W., 1992 (Box 10, Folder 87)
  - MacDowell, Samuel W., 1986 (Box 10, Folder 88)
  - Mack, Maynard, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 89)
  - MacMullen, Edith N., 1985 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - MacMullen, Edith N., 1985 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Mahl, George F., 1988 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Maholmes, Valerie, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Mahoney, Joseph, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Mahoney, Maurice (M.D.), 1976 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Mahota, William J., 1992 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Mahrenholz, Donna, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Malawista, Stephen (M.D.), 1983 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Malherbe, Abraham, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Mandelbrot, Benoit, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Manley, Lawrence, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Mannelidis, Laura, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Marans, Steven R., 1991 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Marchesi, Vincent (M.D.), 1976 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Marcus, Ivan G., 1994 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Marcus, Ruth B., 1988 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Margenau, Henry, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Marguiles, Donald, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Margulis, Grigoriy A., 1991 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Mariano, Nicholas, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Marks, Jonathan, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Marks, Lawrence, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Marmor, Theodore R., 1985 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Marsh, John (M.D.), Undated (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Marshall, Burke, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Marshall, Carol S., 1990 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Marshall, David B., 1994 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Marshall, Rev. Paul, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Marshuetz, Christy, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Martin, Guy V., 1998 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Martin, Natalia, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Martin, Rev. Robert, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Martin, Samuel E., 1994 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Martz, Louis, 1988, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Mashaw, Jerry, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Mason, Dr. John W., 1991 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Mason, Mark, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Massey, William S., 1995 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Matthews, John, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Matthless, Leonard, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Matzkin, Katherine, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - May, Cyril J., 1990 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - May, Georges, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - May, Georges, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Mayes, Linda C., 1990 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Mayhew, David R., 1992 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Maynard, Joseph C., Undated (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Mazzotta, Guiseppe, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - McBride, J. Michael, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - McCance, Thomas Jr., Undated (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - McCarthy, Gregory, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - McCaughey, Arnold Patrick, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - McClatchy, J.D., 1994 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - McClellan, Edwin, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - McCord, Arline F., 1989 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - McCorkle, Barbara, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - McCorkle, Ruth, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - McDermott, Drew, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - McGee, Eleanor Lee, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - McGuire, William J., 1988 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - McKee, J. Braxton (M.D.), Undated (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - McKhann, Charles (M.D.), 1984 (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - McKinley, Paul, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - McNally, Ellen, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - Meeder, Lisa, Undated (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - Meeks, Wayne, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - Meeske, John, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - Meigs, J. Wister (M.D.), 1992 (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - Meinrath, Roberto, Undated (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - Melkus, Gail, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - Mellman, Ira, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - Mellon, Paul, 1968-1992 (Box 11, Folder 73)
  - Mellon, Paul, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 74)
  - Mendelsohn, Robert, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 75)
  - Menocal, Marie, 1998, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 76)
  - Merikangas, Kathleen, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 77)
  - Mermann, Alan, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 78)
  - Merriman, John, 1982, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 79)
  - Merson, Michael H., 1995 (Box 11, Folder 80)
  - Metlitzki, Dorothee, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 81)
  - Meyer, Molly, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 82)
  - Middleton, John F., 1991 (Box 11, Folder 83)
  - Mike-Mayer, Maria, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 84)
  - Miles, George A., 1992 (Box 11, Folder 85)
  - Miller, Christopher L., 1986 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Miller, I. George (M.D.), 1977 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Miller, Joan G., 1988 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Miller, John Perry, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Miller, Joseph A., Undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Miller, Kenneth R., 1987 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Miller, Mary E. (Prof), 2000 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Miller, Neal E., 1988 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Miller, Dr. Perry L., 1988 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Miller, Randolph C., Undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Miller, Spencer F., Undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Mills, David D., 1992 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Millstein, Ira, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Minear, Paul, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Miskimin, Harry A. Jr., 1988, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Mitchell, Margaret, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Mitchell, Martha, Undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Monsen, Susan, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Montanaro, John, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Montecalvo, Linda, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Montgomery, David, 1982, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Montias, J. Michael, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Mood, Eric W., Undated (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Moore, Andrew, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Moore, Gregory, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Moore, Peter B., 1987, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Mordecai, Ben, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Morelli, Frank, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Morgan, Edmund S., 2001 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Morra, Marion E., 1987 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Morse, A. Stephen, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Morton, Barbara J., 1991 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Mostow, George D., 1986 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Mroczkowski, Stanley, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Muehl, E. William, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Mulligan, Kathleen, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Mullinix, Joseph P., 1994 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Murphy, Janet L., 1991 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Murray, Janice, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Murray, Thomas, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Musser, Andrew, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Musto, Dr. David F., 1989 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Myers, Jerome, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Nadel, Ethan R., 1991 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Naftolin, Frederick, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Naigles, Letitia G., 1988 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Napier, B. Davie, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Narendra, Kumipati, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Nash, Lola, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Natanson, Maurice, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Nehorai, Arye, Undated (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Neill, Mary Gardner, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Nelson, Lowry, Jr., 1978 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Nelson, Timothy, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Nestler, Dr. Eric J., 1989 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Newman, Herbert S., 1989 (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Newman,Sasha M, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Niederman, James (M.D.), Undated (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - Niven-Fairchild, Tracy, Undated (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Noon, Patrick, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Nordhaus, William, 1986-2001 (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Noss, Luther, Undated (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - Novick, Dr. Alvin, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - Noyce, Rev. Gaylord, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - Nuland, Sherwin, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - Oberg, Barbara, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - O'Brien, James, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - Odum, William E., 1991 (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - Oemler, Augustus, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 69)
  - Officers Portraits, Undated (Box 12, Folder 70)
  - Officers of Yale University, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 71)
  - Ogletree, Rev. Thomas, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 72)
  - Oliensis, Ellen, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 73)
  - Oliver, Vivian, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 74)
  - Olsen, Douglas, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 75)
  - O'Malley, Stephanie, Undated (Box 12, Folder 76)
  - Onat, Etta S., Undated (Box 12, Folder 77)
  - Onat, E. Turan, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 78)
  - Orcutt, Guy H., Undated (Box 12, Folder 79)
  - Oren, Dr. Daniel, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 80)
  - Ornston, L.Nicholas, 1982, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 81)
  - Orszag, Steven A., Undated (Box 12, Folder 82)
  - Oster, Sharon, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 83)
  - Osterweis, Rollin G., Undated (Box 12, Folder 84)
  - Ostfeild, Adrian, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 85)
  - Ostrom, John H., 1979, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 86)
  - Oundian, Peter, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 87)
  - Outka, Gene, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 88)
  - Packard, Mark, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Pafka, Suzy, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Pagnam, Charles, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Pakes, Ariel, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Palade, George, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Palisca, Claude V., 1991 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Palma, Donald, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Palmer, John J.E., 1978 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Palmer, Robert R., 1970 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Pan, Christopher, Undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Panetti, Joan, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Panjabi, Manohar, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Parisier, Niki, Undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Parisot, Aldo, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Parke, Donna, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Parker, Peter D., 1986 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Parker, William N., 1989 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Patashnik, Eric, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Paterson, Dave, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Patrikis, Peter, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Patterson, Annabel, Undated (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Patterson, D. Helaine, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Patterson, Lee, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Patton, Curtis, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Pearce, David G., 1989 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Pearson, Howard (M.D.), Undated (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Pease, David, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Peck, Merton J., 1990 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Pelikan Jaroslav, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Pelker, Richard (M.D.), Undated (Box 13, Folder 30)